Father,
my incarceration has taught me
how foolish I had been in the past.
I couldn't restrain my greed
and continued to steal.
I'm ashamed of myself.
It's all thanks to you, Father.
Could I please ask for your assistance
in receiving parole?
Recent studies have revealed…
that proper training
can teach even dogs and parrots
how to read, utilize fire,
and understand art.
If that is the case,
then what is the difference
between man and animal?
What do you think?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, about my parole…
Excuse me.
-Hey.
-Got it.
The point is,
after finishing the first cherry
and leaving it in your mouth,
which tooth would you
bite the second with?
You must not bite the first pit
while eating the second cherry.
Sure…
And what about my parole?
I think there's a possibility.
Do you really, Father?
I will recommend you to the committee.
Thank you, Fa--
I quite like
your mischievous habit of theft.
Truly, an evil disposition
cannot be corrected.
However,
I cannot deny this talent.
You will prove useful to me.
I cannot let Jotaro's Stand
leave this prison, after all.
EPISODE 9: DEBT COLLECTOR MARY LYNN MANSON
What the hell?
What do you mean F.F. is hiding it?
It's an important disc
containing your father's Stand, right?
Are you fine with not knowing
where she's hiding it?
-How do we know we can--
-This place is fun!
-It's not like the wetlands at all!
-Really, now.
I want to play too.
It's called "catch," right?
I trust F.F.,
and Pale Snake doesn't know
that she's alive.
It's the safest place.
You're right.
But it would be even better
if you could deliver the disc to him.
I know.
But I'm not allowed visitors or
phone calls because I attempted to escape.
And I don't have a plan
to carry it out yet.
Hey, you!
That's my drink!
What's the matter with you?
I'm thirsty.
Put that cup back on the bench now!
If it's that important to you,
then don't put it down.
Especially in here.
F.F., I'll bring you more water!
Don't cause any trouble!
Give it back!
Oh, well.
I ended up with more water. Lucky me!
All right,
let's get back to playing.
-Jeez.
-What?
You've never thrown a ball, have you?
Oh, crap.
Tuck your hips in.
A bit more.
You got it.
Your form's looking better already.
Jolyne, did you know
that we've tossed the ball 86 times now?
We haven't dropped it at all.
Think we can reach a hundred?
A hundred dollars says it won't last.
I bet 100 dollars.
Sorry, but who are you?
What do you mean 100 dollars?
I'm Miraschon,
inmate FE26789.
I'm betting 100 dollars
that you won't be able to
make it to the 100th throw.
Where did that come from, all of a sudden?
I'm just killing time.
Let's do it!
We only have 13 more throws!
You keep quiet!
I don't have that kind of money.
I can't match this wager.
You can bet any item.
Tobacco, drugs,
gum, a phone call, a vibrator…
I'll accept anything valuable.
Let me be frank.
I'm not betting on anything.
Hold it.
Jolyne,
we should accept this bet.
It's a chance to make money.
You can use my money.
F.F. might suck at playing catch,
but still managed to continue to 87.
We can win!
Come on, Ermes.
You suspect that this is
Pale Snake's trap.
But I know that Miraschon
because we're on the same floor.
She's the greedy self-destructive type
that kept committing petty theft.
Think about it.
Even after your restrictions get lifted,
you need to buy your time on the phone.
So,
gonna play or not?
I want to give it a go! We can win this!
Good.
But you don't have 100 dollars, do you?
If you raise your voice or get too close,
the bet is immediately off.
Got it?
The wager has already begun.
But it wouldn't be fair for me
if you play too close
or hold onto the ball too long.
We'll stay at least three meters away
and throw within ten seconds.
Good.
Time to play ball! Let's go.
Don't rush and take your aim.
You have a whole ten seconds
before you throw!
Eighty-nine.
Only 11 more throws to go!
Bitch, stay away from my cup!
F.F.!
That was close.
Come on, focus!
It wasn't my fault!
It's her! She got near my water!
I'm just enjoying the show.
Just stay away from my cup!
All right.
Five more seconds.
F.F., throw the ball!
-Damn, she's distracting me!
-Hey!
I'll hold your cup for you.
-One second left.
-F.F.!
Idiot!
Jolyne!
That was close, but she caught it.
Sorry, I panicked.
Be careful next time, F.F.
I'm fine now!
See? A hundred throws!
Good.
I can go another hundred throws!
See? An easy win.
Now, give us the 100 dollars.
Hold on, she made a wager with F.F. too.
That makes it 200 dollars.
That's true. She owes us 200 dollars.
Now, cough it up.
A thousand dollars
if you throw a hundred more.
You heard me.
I said let's play for 1,000 dollars.
Are you serious?
Do you even have that much money?
Of course, I do.
But like I said,
I'll take anything valuable too.
The rules will be the same as last time.
What do you say?
No, I'm done playing with you.
I'm going to be frank.
There's something I don't like about you.
-If you want to wager, go play else--
-I'll play.
Good.
F.F., hand me the glove and the ball.
-Okay!
-Ermes, no!
Jolyne, you're right, she is suspicious.
Especially the way she insists on betting.
But…
we can potentially make 1,200 dollars.
There's no way we can pass that up.
Be careful, though.
The game begins
the moment you agree to play.
Might be 10 seconds soon.
-Ermes!
-F.F.!
More easy money.
Thirty.
Thirty-one.
Thirty-two.
Great, the next one makes it 33.
Inmates, put away your exercise equipment!
Recess time is over!
Five…
F.F.!
Thirty-three!
Bitch!
What's with that attitude?!
Hey, this bet is off. Got that?
Let's say that a meteorite falls
from the skies above
into this yard right now.
Then, you'll persuade to end the game,
blaming it on the meteorite.
Not to convince me,
but yourselves.
Does that sit well with you, though?
Maybe you ran out of time
because you took too long
to throw the ball.
If you can honestly say
that you didn't break
the rules of the game,
then go ahead,
end this game.
Dammit…
Ermes,
you know you'll be thrown in
the Punishment Ward.
Please, mister.
Give me five… No, three minutes.
I'll make another round,
so finish up in two minutes.
F.F., hurry!
But a measly 100 dollars
only pays for the ball.
I'm putting the glove away. Give it to me!
What?
Goddammit!
Shit…
I attached a sticker to it
in case something like this happens!
Ermes!
Whoa!
Let's keep playing.
I'm just watching.
I won't interfere or object.
And I can't prove anything, but…
Ermes…
She knows what she's done.
Without a doubt,
she violated the rules
of the game just now.
I know this
because Mary Lynn Manson,
the debt collector, appeared.
Ermes!
She's a Stand User!
Mary Lynn Manson
will always collect the debt
no matter where you hide it,
or what it is. All of it.
That's not enough.
Smack…
It's game over.
Ermes!
Ermes…
If I sell this liver on the black market,
it will compensate for
the remaining 590 dollars.
Bastard!
Take this!
I am the shadow of Ermes's conscience.
You cannot attack me.
Ermes broke the rules and lost the bet.
I only collected her debt.
If you have any other valuable,
I can exchange it for this liver.
The bet's not over yet.
What?
One thousand throws.
If I win,
give back everything you took from her.
Everything.
Good. However, I hope you are prepared
to wager something as valuable.
I'm aware.
Very well.
The game has already started.
I shall see you again.
F.F.!
Jolyne.
Ermer, this wasn't your fault.
Miraschon is a Stand User.
Pale Snake must have a hand in this.
She must be here to collect
my father's disc from me.
Then you really shouldn't play this game.
You got caught in
me and my father's problem.
I can't let you die.
But what are you going to do?
A thousand throws?
That Stand seems invincible.
You're right.
We'll chase Miraschon herself
and beat her!
The Stand may be invincible,
but Miraschon isn't.
That's why she ran.
Let's go!
She's here.
She must have entered this room.
There's a door to the back.
Maybe she escaped that way.
F.F.!
Jolyne, don't throw it yet!
Crap!
F.F.! It's coming towards you!
Where is it? I can't see a thing!
Don't move!
The ball will hit you!
Whoa! I got it!
That was too close!
Great job, F.F.
Now, calm down so you can throw it back.
I'm right here!
-Where are you?
-Hurry!
It's over for them.
F.F.!
I don't have time for this!
F.F.
I shot towards
the direction of her voice.
I didn't even aim!
Dammit! What is she?
Lockdown will soon commence.
All inmates must return to their cells.
Prepare for headcount.
I repeat!
She ran to the right!
How unfortunate.
You can't run anymore.
Now that we know
that you are a Stand User,
I won't hold back.
Wait,
I'll give it all back.
The liver…
and the money too!
That's not enough.
Who gave you that Stand ability?
What?
Pale Snake.
It was him, wasn't it?
I want to know who his User is.
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't test me.
I'm serious!
I only wanted to go on parole!
What is this?
This is an elevator
for transporting cafeteria food.
How many more seconds?
Six…
No, is it five?
Jolyne!
Two seconds left…
F.F, the ball!
Throw it to me!
Dammit!
What's your next move?
Eight seconds left.
Seven, six…
F.F.!
Will this do, Miraschon?
Such an easy and simple request.
Feel free to ask me again.
The game of catch
was just interrupted.
It's game over,
Jolyne Cujoh!
Mary Lynn Manson
will always collect what's owed!
No matter where it is,
even if you don't know where,
Mary Lynn knows where it is.
Jolyne!
I'll take the most expensive organ.
And for the remainder,
your most prized possession,
your father's disc.
And the disc…
was on her since the beginning!
I won!
Your organ,
your disc…
They're all mine now!
The game of catch isn't over yet.
But how?
The ball…
Impossible.
-You broke the rules.
-No.
We never agreed on my partner.
The guard is okay too, right?
The debt collector agrees with me.
How many throws do I have left? Is it 800?
Or 900?
It's a pain to count.
Let's say 1,000 throws.
We did it!
MIRASCHON
STAND: DEBT COLLECTOR MARY LYNN MANSON
OUT OF COMMISSION
I will return the disc to my father.
Along with the other disc
that Pale Snake has.
No matter what.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter